mousesavers.com 2006-03-26

# MouseSavers.com - Privacy Policy & Other Legal Stuff

|  |  |  |  |   
---|---|---|---|---  
|  |  |  |   
|  | 

#####  Find out how to save on: 

#####  [Walt Disney World](http://www.mousesavers.com/wdw.html)

#####  [Disneyland](http://www.mousesavers.com/disneyland.html)

##### [Disney Cruise Line](http://www.mousesavers.com/dcl.html)

#####  [Transportation for Your Disney Vacation](http://www.mousesavers.com/transportation.html)

##### [Other Disney Travel Savings](http://www.mousesavers.com/misc.html)

#####  [Discount Disney Shopping Mall](http://www.mousesavers.com/merchandise.html)

#####  [Live Disney Shows](http://www.mousesavers.com/liveshows.html)

##### [Disney Freebies](http://www.mousesavers.com/free.html)

##### [Other Disney Vacations](http://www.mousesavers.com/otherdisney.html)

##### [Non-Disney Theme Parks & Attractions](http://www.mousesavers.com/otherparks.html)

#####  More information:

#####  [About MouseSavers](http://www.mousesavers.com/aboutmousesavers.html)

##### [Frequently Asked Questions](http://www.mousesavers.com/faq.html)

#####  [Trip Reports and Articles](http://www.mousesavers.com/tripreports.html)

##### [Links](http://www.mousesavers.com/links.html)

##### [Testimonials](http://www.mousesavers.com/testimonials.html)

#####  [Privacy Policy & Legal Stuff](http://www.mousesavers.com/privacy.html)

##### [Contact Mary](http://www.mousesavers.com/contact.html)

|   |   
|  |  |  |   
|  |  |  |   
  
###  Privacy Policy & Other Legal Stuff

#### Privacy Policy

It's really very simple. MouseSavers.com® will not sell or share your personal information with any outside organization or company.

Any personally identifiable information you provide through the newsletter registration on MouseSavers.com is used by the site only to send you the MouseSavers Newsletter (and the Hot Deals announcements, if you opt into that list). You can cancel your newsletter and/or Hot Deals announcement subscriptions at any time. [Click here](http://www.mousesavers.com/newsletterhelp.html#unsubscribe) to learn how. 

Any personally identifiable information you provide when entering a contest sponsored by MouseSavers.com is used by the site only to select winners and award prizes. Non-winning entries are deleted or destroyed at the completion of the contest and your information is not shared with third parties unless you give your explicit permission to do so. 

Testimonials on the site are unsolicited and are reprinted with the authors' permission. Last names are abbreviated for privacy purposes. 

MouseSavers.com contains external links to other sites that may gather, sell or share personal information. Please see the linked site's privacy policy for details. 

####  Cookies and IP Address Tracking

MouseSavers.com® uses a simple cookie that expires after 2 hours, combined with basic IP address tracking software, in order to count how many unique visitors come to the site. The information gathered is used only for compiling visitor statistics. At no time is it linked with any personally identifiable information.

MouseSavers.com also contains external links to other sites that may employ cookies and/or IP address tracking.

####  Legal Disclaimers

MouseSavers.com® is not an official site of The Walt Disney Company or of Universal Studios.

All information on this site is unofficial and subject to change without notice, and the author shall not be held liable for any incorrect information, errors or omissions in the material presented here.

Please call hotels, airlines, restaurants, merchants, theme parks and/or resorts directly, or visit their official web pages to confirm critical information before your visit. 

While the author makes a conscientious effort to find great deals on travel, entertainment and miscellaneous merchandise, MouseSavers.com may not always offer the lowest price available. 

MouseSavers.com links to other web sites that may be of interest to readers. No guarantee is made regarding the quality, value or reliability of external sites, nor is MouseSavers.com responsible for the privacy policies or the content of external web sites. 

####  Trademark and Copyright Notices

MouseSavers.com® is a registered trademark of MouseSavers, Inc., 5045 Chipita Pines Drive, Cascade, CO 80809.

Content of MouseSavers.com is © Mary Waring & MouseSavers, Inc. 2001-2006. Text and photos from this website may not be reproduced in whole or in part without written permission from the copyright holder.

Disneyland®, Walt Disney World®, Disney Cruise Line®, Magic Kingdom®, Epcot®, Disney's Animal Kingdom®, Disney's FASTPASS®, Park Hopper®, Downtown Disney®, DisneyQuest®, Disney's Wide World of Sportstm, All-Star Cafe®, Disney's California Adventuretm, Disney's Paradise Piersm, Disney's Grand Californian Hotel®, Disney Magic® and Disney Wonder® are trademarks of the Walt Disney Company. 

As to Disney artwork, logos and properties: © Disney 

Universal Studios®, UNIVERSAL Orlandosm, Universal Studios Vacationstm, Universal Studios Islands of Adventuretm, Universal Studios Floridatm, Universal Studios CityWalk Orlandotm and Orlando FlexTickettm are trademarks of Universal Studios. 

As to Universal artwork, logos and properties: © Universal Studios 

Back to top

Content of MouseSavers.com is © Mary Waring & MouseSavers, Inc. 2001-2006. Text and photos from this website may not be reproduced in whole or in part without written permission from the copyright holder.
